WEICHENG HUNG

Front-end Developer



PROFILE

I am a highly adaptable individual with a strong ability to seamlessly integrate into teams. However, I never compromise on the meticulousness of my work, ensuring that I consistently deliver applications of the utmost quality. Given the ever-evolving landscape of front-end technologies, I proactively enrich my expertise and development skills to stay at the forefront of industry trends.

CONTACT

0988-788-290

weicheng2138@gmail.com

weicheng.dev

EDUCATION

Master @ National Center University

Graduate Institute of Industrial Management 2013 - 2017

Bachelor @ National Changhua University of Education

Department of Mathematics 2009 - 2013

RELEVANT SKILLS

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES6), HTML, CSS, Python

Libraries & Frameworks

Vue, Node.js, React

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer @ President Information CORP.

October 2021 - Present

- Develop Frontend of E-Commerce and SCM backend (Call off)
- Develop and Containerize the Service of Google Speech-To-Text for Product Search Bar

R&D Substitute @ National Taiwan University

August 2017 - June 2021

- Construct Internal Inventory System for lab by using RFID, Vue.js, Bootstrap and Firebase.
- Lab MIS.
- Six-axis Robot arm Controlling.
- Project execution which related to chemical engineering.
- Side Project: Nuxt portfolio with Tailwindcss and StoryBlok.
- Side Project: Taifex data crawling and electron-vue desktop app.

Co-Founder @ Anhe Three Dimensional Co.

August 2015 - July 2017

- Algorithm implementation with Java which is refer to Zhang (2015).
- Design human interface for inkjet 3D printer with Vaadin and Three.js.
- Construct internal system with Angular 2, Spring Boot Rest API and using MySQL as data source.

SAP Student Instructor @ National Center University

June 2014 - July 2015

- SAP ERP student team leader of production planning.
- SAP product planning instructor for EMBA students.